+55 (11) 99577-9119

contato@danielnaoexiste.dev || danieldenardo1@gmail.com

Portfolio: danielnaoexiste.dev || Github: github.com/danielnaoexiste || LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/danielnaoexiste

# Daniel Gazzaneo Denardo

#### SUMMARY

Front-end developer specialized in React, React Native and Vue. Currently graduating in Information Systems at UNIFEI - Brazil. Experience in version control systems (Git/Github), design system development, object-oriented programming, agile methodologies (scrum/kanban) and game development with Unity(C#) and Godot(GDScript).

## **SKILLS**

```
Languages: Javascript; PHP; Python; Lua; GML; C#; C/C++.
Frameworks: Vue JS; React; React-Native; Bootstrap; NodeJS; ExpressJS;
Handlebars.
Game Development: Unity, Godot, GameMaker: Studio, Love2D.
```

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Aiqfome** - Front-End Developer

SINCE MAY 2021

Responsible for the development of front-end applications in React. Development of dashboards and action managers (NDA); Experience in agile (scrum/kanban); UI/UX Design; Code Review. React-Query / Micro Frontends / Styled-Components / React Hook Form / Design Systems / il8next.

## **Hivelabs** - Front-End Developer

SEP 2020 - MAY 2021

Responsible for the development of front-end applications in Vue JS and React. Application development in partnership with Locaweb All iN (Squads); REST APIs with NodeJS / Express and integration of SOAP interfaces. UX / UI Design. Vuetify / Styled-Components / Bootstrap / Handlebars / Materialize / Semantic / i18n.

#### **Hivelabs** — Web Development Internship

FEB 2020 - SEP 2020

Development of backend systems with Node.JS / Express and Front End with React and React Native. Responsible for the implementation of digital marketing systems. Google Tag Manager / Handlebars / Bootstrap.

# **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

## Dev-U, UNIFEI - Programming Director

NOVEMBER 2019 - MAY 2020

Game developer in Godot and Unity. Responsible for training and managing the programming sector. Lectures on game development and game jams.

## Dev-U, UNIFEI - Programmer

SEPTEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019

Responsible for developing games in Godot (GDScript) and Unity (C#) for game jams and personal projects.

# **EDUCATION**

SINCE FEBRUARY 2018

Federal University of Itajubá (UNIFEI), Itajubá — Information Systems (Bachelor's)

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Portuguese: Native

English: Advanced (C2 Proficient)